[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "You are using multiple address handling in a sales document. At which levels can you assign the address determination?",
    "options": [
      "Address usage of the business partner",
      "Origin and source of the partner function",
      "Generic partner function",
      "Partner determination procedure"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "When a user creates a sales order with reference to a quotation, a header text must be automatically copied from the sold-to party if it cannot be found in quotation...",
    "options": [
      "Assign an appropriate text type to the sales document type.",
      "Include the text type with an appropriate access sequence in the text determination procedure.",
      "Ensure that the access sequence reads the sold-to party text first.",
      "In the access sequence, set the partner function language for this text to 'sold-to party'.",
      "Assign the text determination procedure to the sales document type."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["B", "D", "E"]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "To which elements do you assign a partner determination procedure?",
    "options": [
      "Delivery item category",
      "Business partner category",
      "Sales item category",
      "Account group",
      "Delivery type"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C", "D", "E"]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of decision table processing as used in SAP S/4HANA output management?",
    "options": [
      "Every table row is processed in sequence. In each row, every condition column cell is processed from right to left.",
      "It is possible to maintain one condition column cell with multiple result column cells for each table row.",
      "Every condition column is processed in sequence. In each condition column, every row is processed from top to bottom.",
      "It is possible to evaluate the content of condition column cells by using comparison operators or value ranges."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A"]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which channels are supported by SAP S/4HANA output management?",
    "options": ["ALE", "Fax", "E-mail", "XML", "Print"],
    "correct_answers": ["C", "D", "E"]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Texts are copied from a sold-to party to a sales order. Any later change to the sold-to party texts should not be visible in this order. Which object controls this behavior?",
    "options": [
      "Text determination procedure",
      "Access sequence",
      "Text procedure assignment",
      "Text ID"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A"]
  },
   {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which of the following settings are required to be able to deliver a product?",
    "options": [
      "You need to set the Schedule Lines Allowed indicator in the item category.",
      "You need to set up the item category as relevant for delivery-related billing.",
      "You need to set up copying control in Logistics Execution System for the item category.",
      "You need to set the Item Relevant for Delivery indicator in the item category."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "B"]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which controls can you set when you configure a schedule line category?",
    "options": [
      "Create delivery group",
      "Delivery relevance",
      "Structure scope",
      "Goods movement type"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["B", "D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "You sell a product for which there is a bill of material. What must you set to ensure that the components automatically appear as sub-items in the order?",
    "options": [
      "The item usage during the item category determination of each sub-item",
      "The delivery group in the item category of the sub-item",
      "The material entry type in the sales document type",
      "The structure scope in the item category of the main item"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "A reason for rejection has been set against a sales order item. Why is the net value of the item still included in the total net value of the order?",
    "options": [
      "The reason for rejection was not assigned to the item category.",
      "The reason for rejection does not have the appropriate configuration to exclude item value.",
      "The item value is used statistically hence added to the net value.",
      "The update of the net value is not triggered after the rejection of the item."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "You want to determine the item category in a sales document. What do you need to consider?",
    "options": [
      "The customer master data",
      "The sales organization",
      "The higher-level item",
      "The material master data"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C", "D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "How do you restrict the reasons for rejection for a sales document?",
    "options": [
      "Assign the permitted reasons for rejection to the relevant sales document type.",
      "Assign the permitted reasons for rejection to the relevant sales item category.",
      "Specify the permitted reasons for rejection in the relevant customer master.",
      "Specify the permitted reasons for rejection in the customer material info record."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A"]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "When you create a sales order with reference to a quotation, you want to ensure the entire quotation is always included in the order. Where do you make this setting?",
    "options": [
      "Copying control",
      "Order type",
      "Order item category",
      "Quotation type"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A"]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "You normally include multiple sales orders in your outbound deliveries. Which sales order fields would prevent this from happening if their content was different?",
    "options": [
      "Route",
      "Plant",
      "Material group",
      "Shipping point",
      "Ship-to party"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "D", "E"]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What settings should you make to ensure precise scheduling is used when the system performs delivery scheduling?",
    "options": [
      "Maintain the transit time in the route in hours and minutes.",
      "Assign a shift sequence to the working times.",
      "Assign a set of working times to the plant.",
      "Assign a set of working times to the shipping point.",
      "Maintain shifts defining the times for starting and ending work."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C", "D", "E"]
  },
   {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "When determining a storage location during delivery processing, the system uses a rule defined in which of the following?",
    "options": [
      "Outbound delivery type",
      "Material",
      "Outbound delivery item category",
      "Shipping point"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A"]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "When an outbound delivery is created for a sales order, from which object does the system determine the default delivery type to be used?",
    "options": [
      "Sales order item category",
      "Shipping point",
      "Shipping conditions",
      "Sales order type"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "You want to be able to create and goods issue an outbound delivery for a stock material. What settings should you make?",
    "options": [
      "Define the goods movement type in the delivery item category.",
      "Set the order item category to be relevant for delivery.",
      "Set the schedule line category to be relevant for delivery.",
      "Activate schedule lines allowed in the order item category.",
      "Define the goods movement type in the schedule line category."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C", "D", "E"]
  },
   {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Which fields are used in the determination of the shipping point?",
    "options": [
      "Transportation group",
      "Plant",
      "Shipping conditions",
      "Sales document type",
      "Loading group"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["B", "C", "E"]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Which decisions do you have to make when configuring a new delivery item category?",
    "options": [
      "Whether a delivery should be split by warehouse number",
      "Whether over-delivery is allowed",
      "Whether the route should be redetermined",
      "Whether a storage location should be determined"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["B", "D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Which fields are used to determine the delivery item category?",
    "options": [
      "Item category group",
      "Shipping point",
      "MRP type",
      "Higher-level item category",
      "Delivery type"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "D", "E"]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What are some features of the Sales Order Fulfillment Issues app?",
    "options": [
      "The process flow can be used to directly resolve issues as quickly as possible.",
      "The app shows cost simulations for all possible order fulfillment scenarios.",
      "Icons and colors are used in the app to represent different types of issues.",
      "The app allows a user to monitor sales orders in critical stages and efficiently address issues."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of a service item in a sales order?",
    "options": [
      "The material has a specific item category group.",
      "The item in the sales order is blocked for delivery.",
      "The Delivering Plant field is not required.",
      "The service item has no schedule line assigned."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A"]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What are some of the prerequisites for the creation of a credit memo based on a credit memo request?",
    "options": [
      "The Billing Block field in the credit memo request must be empty.",
      "Copying control must exist between the sales document and the billing document.",
      "The billing document of the original customer invoice must be cancelled.",
      "An appropriate reason for rejection must be assigned to the original sales order item."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What are some characteristics of the process flow in SAP S/4HANA?",
    "options": [
      "The process flow supports direct navigation to applications that can be used to solve problems.",
      "Issue solving is supported by a wizard based on machine learning (ML).",
      "The status of a document is updated using artificial intelligence (AI) algorithms.",
      "Color coding is used to indicate the status of a document."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "How can you enable partial deliveries for a sales order, while making sure to get as few deliveries as possible?",
    "options": [
      "In each order item, set Complete Delivery to required.",
      "In the order header, set Order Combination to allowed.",
      "In the order header, set the Complete Delivery indicator.",
      "In each order item, set Partial Deliveries to required."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "When performing backorder processing, which confirmation strategies can you select?",
    "options": [
      "Drop",
      "Fill",
      "Redistribute",
      "Gain",
      "Obtain"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["B", "C", "D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "The delivering plant should be determined automatically for a sales order item. Which master data sources can be used to achieve this?",
    "options": [
      "Sold-to party",
      "Material master",
      "Customer material info record",
      "Ship-to party",
      "Material determination"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "B", "C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "Which documents can only be created with reference to a billing document?",
    "options": [
      "Invoice correction request",
      "Debit memo request",
      "Returns order",
      "Invoice cancellation"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Which time components are used to calculate the confirmed delivery date in a sales order?",
    "options": [
      "Loading time of the shipping point",
      "Transportation lead time of the forwarding agent",
      "Transit time of the route",
      "Pick/pack time of the warehouse number"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What are the effects of posting the goods issue during a sales process?",
    "options": [
      "Delivery requirements in material planning are updated.",
      "The document flow is updated.",
      "The overall status of the delivery is set to complete.",
      "The warehouse task status is set to complete.",
      "The billing document can now be created."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "B", "E"]
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "You want to evaluate sales discount condition records. Which tool can you use?",
    "options": [
      "Price lists",
      "Pricing reports",
      "Listing",
      "Manage Prices - Sales app"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "You want to change the default description of a specific condition type for selected condition records. How can you achieve this?",
    "options": [
      "Use the Manage Prices - Sales app.",
      "Use the Change condition (VK12) transaction.",
      "Use report COND_AV.",
      "Use the Creation of Pricing Lists app."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "B"]
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "In your pricing procedure you have several condition types for a price such as PROO, PR02, PN00 and HM00. Only one of these prices is taken into account. Which setting causes this behavior?",
    "options": [
      "Condition function",
      "Exclusion indicator",
      "Condition class",
      "Header condition"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "You want to use condition exclusion. For which of the following pricing elements can you set the condition exclusion indicator?",
    "options": [
      "Condition type",
      "Condition type groups",
      "Condition record",
      "Condition category"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "What must every condition record contain?",
    "options": [
      "Scale",
      "Quantity",
      "Validity period",
      "Calculation type"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C", "D"]
  },
   {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "You want to set up automatic pricing in a sales order. Which actions should you take to achieve this?",
    "options": [
      "Set up condition tables and assign them to the relevant access sequences.",
      "Set up condition tables and assign them to the relevant condition types.",
      "Set up condition types and assign them to the relevant pricing procedure.",
      "Set up the pricing procedure and assign it to the relevant sales document type."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "You want to set up a discount with a scale value (condition type K029) that is based on the material group 'spare parts'. The discount should be granted for all items in a sales order that are spare parts. What do you need to set up for condition type K029 so it meets this requirement?",
    "options": [
      "You need to set the Condition Index indicator for condition type K029.",
      "You need to set up condition type K029 as a group condition.",
      "You need to set the Condition Update indicator for condition type K029.",
      "You need to set up condition type K029 as a header condition."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["B"]
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "You maintain a sales order with several items and apply a manual freight charge. The system should automatically distribute the freight charge among the items based on the net value. What do you need to do?",
    "options": [
      "Set up the freight charge as a header condition.",
      "Set up calculation type B (fixed amount) for the freight charge.",
      "Set up condition type groups for the freight charge.",
      "Assign a group condition routine to the freight charge."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C"]
  },
   {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "Which of the following is a prerequisite for billing?",
    "options": [
      "You need an order item category that is configured to be billing relevant.",
      "You need a sales document type that is configured to be billing relevant.",
      "You need an billing item category that is configured to be billing relevant.",
      "You need a billing type that is configured to be billing relevant."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A"]
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "Which of the following are characteristics of an invoice list process?",
    "options": [
      "You must create an invoice list at specified time intervals or on specific dates.",
      "You must set up a periodic billing plan for the invoice list creation.",
      "You must send the payer a single invoice list instead of the individual invoices.",
      "You use preliminary billing documents for the invoice list creation."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "Where do you configure the default billing type to be used for delivery-related billing?",
    "options": [
      "Sales document type",
      "Delivery type",
      "Sales document item category",
      "Copying control"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A"]
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "What can you configure in a billing type?",
    "options": [
      "Billing type for cancellation",
      "Reference mandatory indicator",
      "Default delivery type for billing",
      "Item number increment"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "D"]
  },
   {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "What are some of the differences between the Create Billing Documents (VF04) transaction and the Create Billing Documents - Billing Due List Items app?",
    "options": [
      "With the app, a user can set default billing blocks for sales documents.",
      "With transaction VF04, a user can cancel a collective billing run.",
      "With transaction VF04, a user can generate a log for the collective run.",
      "With the app, a user can block the automatic posting of billing documents."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C", "D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "Which of the following is a use case for a billing plan type?",
    "options": [
      "Invoice lists",
      "Milestone billing",
      "Settlement management",
      "Convergent billing"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["B"]
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "You want to use billing as part of the sales process. Which organizational units must be configured?",
    "options": [
      "Company code",
      "Sales organization",
      "Business area",
      "Profit center"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "B"]
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "How does the system determine the warehouse number in an order-to-cash process?",
    "options": [
      "It is linked to a combination of plant and distribution channel.",
      "It is linked to a combination of plant and shipping point.",
      "It is linked to a combination of plant and storage location.",
      "It is linked to a combination of sales area and plant."
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "question": "You want to process and monitor outbound deliveries. Which organizational unit supports this?",
    "options": [
      "Distribution channel",
      "Warehouse number",
      "Plant",
      "Shipping point"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["D"]
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "question": "Which information comes from the payer?",
    "options": [
      "Invoicing list scheduling",
      "Payment terms",
      "Billing plan",
      "Billing address"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "B"]
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "question": "Which business partner categories can you use to create customer master records?",
    "options": [
      "Company",
      "Group",
      "Organization",
      "Sold-to party"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["B", "C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "question": "Which field from the material master is used in route determination in a sales order?",
    "options": [
      "Weight group",
      "Loading group",
      "Transportation group",
      "Material freight group"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "question": "You save a sales order and receive a system message that a business partner of a specific partner function is missing. Which of the following partner functions can cause this problem?",
    "options": [
      "Ship-to party (SH)",
      "Sold-to party (SP)",
      "Invoicing party (11)",
      "Ordering party (1)"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "B"]
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "question": "When you create a business partner, allocation of the business partner number is controlled by a number range assigned to which object?",
    "options": [
      "Account group",
      "Business partner category",
      "Business partner grouping",
      "Business partner role"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "question": "You are a consultant on an SAP S/4HANA Cloud greenfield project. As part of their clean core journey, the customer must analyze the current IT landscape to eliminate redundant systems and establish an efficient architectural design. Which of the following can you use to do the analysis?",
    "options": [
      "SAP Cloud ALM",
      "Lean IX",
      "SAP Best Practices",
      "SAP Solution Manager"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "question": "You are a consultant on an SAP S/4HANA Cloud greenfield project. Which of the following aspects should you focus on to achieve and maintain clean core data quality?",
    "options": [
      "Stability",
      "Accuracy",
      "Efficiency",
      "Timeliness"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "C"]
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "question": "Which of the following API types does SAP recommend to use to achieve clean core integrations?",
    "options": [
      "OData",
      "SOAP",
      "RFC",
      "IDoc"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["A", "B"]
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "question": "You are a consultant on an SAP S/4HANA Cloud brownfield project. In a meeting the customer decides to remodel an existing business process in accordance with clean core principles. Which of the following SAP Signavio solutions can be used for the remodeling?",
    "options": [
      "SAP Signavio Process Insights",
      "SAP Signavio Process Governance",
      "SAP Signavio Process Manager",
      "SAP Signavio Process Intelligence"
    ],
    "correct_answers": ["B", "C"]
  }






]
